thanks for dinner mom
it was really good
yeah the soup was amazing
I'm glad you liked it too bad dad couldn't eat with us
he had to work late but don't worry
I saved him some uh
I think I'm gonna head to my room
I've got homework to do hold on Mike
aren't you forgetting something
what it's your turn to do the dishes
but you didn't do the dishes yesterday
actually I did
but you only washed three plates yesterday
there are way more dishes today
it's not my fault that we had pizzas yesterday
and a big meal today that's not fair
life isn't fair sometimes
but I did the dishes on both Thanksgiving and Christmas
did I complain no
mom say something
you can't just let him get away with that
your brother has a point Mike
you take turns doing the dishes that's fair
alright
actually I can do the dishes today really
really but only if you wipe down the table
and take out the trash deal
isn't it muddy outside it just stopped raining
exactly mom
that's why
I'd rather do the dishes than take out the trash